boy Ildar from Neftekamsk Uh-huh sold
мальчик Ильдар из Нефтекамска Угу продал
his property and left for
своё имущество и уехал в оккупированный
Russian-occupied Crimea
Россией Крым
Uh-huh A few years later, the Armed Forces of
Угу Через несколько лет Вооружённые силы
Ukraine, with the support of NATO, began the
Украины при поддержке НАТО начали
procedure for the liberation of Crimea and its
процедуру освобождения Крыма и его
demilitarization
демилитаризации
question How many
вопрос На сколько
bucks is the boy Ildar
баксов мальчик Ильдар
very interesting
очень интересный
question Hello What are you talking about
вопрос Здравствуйте О чём общаетесь
yes In everything, on what  kuro on the beach
да Во всём пожи на каком куро на пляже
from the city of Khmelnitsk
из города Хмельницке
where Yes, I understood from Krasnodar that you have
откуда Да я с Краснодара понял у вас там
topsa there, it’s a beach
топса это пляжный
city  Well,
город Ну на море
there’s a beach at sea And there’s an oil
поня пляж А есть нефтеперерабатывающий
refinery, like in Tops Yes, I guess I don’t know
завод вроде в топса Да наверное не знаю
There, like a couple of days, a Ukrainian
Там же типа пару дней украинский
drone flew in that the oil refinery was on fire, the
беспилотник прилетел что горил
vacuum
нефтеперерабатывающий завод вакуумная
unit was out of order
установка выведена из строя
Yes, I guess I know, honestly, it’s cool, not
Да Наверно я зна честно прикольно не то
that you understood, in short, what are you talking about the beach
что ты понял короче да как ты про пляж
og you beach by the way I say cool
ог ты пля кста Я говорю классный
PJ and
ПЖ а
those a brains I don’t have enough brains
те а мозгов не У меня достаточно мозгов
at least they took me to school I work hay to
как минимум в школу взяли работаю сено в
school to work who do you work at school
школу на работу кем ты в школе работаешь
chuz
чуз
hands  It’s been a year and a half since I
рукам уже полтора года как ну как диплом
received my diploma, but show me your work book, don’t
получил да покажи трудовую книжку не
open it. Just show me that it’s
открывай Просто покажи что она
there. You have to follow it.
есть Это надо идти за ней Ну не реально
Well, it’s not realistic, you don’t look like a
вот ты не похожа на учителя
school teacher. I’ll wait through government services. It won’t work.
школьного Я подожду через госуслуги
Show me your physical
пойдёт не Покажи физическую
work book. Well, if grandma is sleeping there,
книжку трудовую Ну если там бабушка спит
there’s  she is a grandmother in her grandmother's
есть она бабушка бабушке в
pocket. I mean, in her room in the closet in the
кармане В смысле в её комнате в шкафу в
closet is Wait Stop Yours Your
шкафу лежит Подожди Стоп Твои Твои
personal documents yes They are in the grandmother's
личные документы да Они у бабушки в
room Well the closet is there and all the
комнате Ну шкаф находится там и там все
documents are there I don't use  every day with
документы Я же не пользуюсь каждый день
these documents I didn’t realize that
этими документами мне не послышалось что
you are an adult man who has already graduated from
ты взрослый мужик который уже закончил
university and works and works at a room
университет и работает да работает в рум
school, keeps things in your grandmother’s room
школе вещи держит в комнате бабушки
Yes, I came to visit my grandmother for the weekend Yes, that’s
Да я приехал на выходные к бабушке
all, you came with a work book to visit your
Да все при ты приехал с трудовой книжкой
grandmother for the weekend Yes, that’s how it lies
на выходные к бабушке Да так она лежит
at home Are you now at home with your grandmother or at home at
дома Ты сейчас дома у бабушки или дома у
your place?
себя ня бауш в с
I have it in my passport Well, in the
собой у меня в паспорте находится Ну в
cover
обложке
Yara and labor are in my place,
Яре и трудовая находятся у меня
absolutely everything is here Edik, in short,
абсолютно тут все Эдик ты короче
you are unique at 22 years old, keep it with your
уникальный ти в 22 года держать у
grandmother, in short,
бабушки короче
and you cling to your grandmother. I’m
а ты прицепился к бабушке Я
here to
здесь
specifically show that there are some grandmother’s
специально покажи что есть бабушкины
things. Well, don’t go into
вещи какие-то Ну не заходи в комнату к
grandma's room Show me grandma's shoes or jacket
бабушке Покажи там обувь или куртка
so I can understand that you're
бабушки чтобы я понял что ты
really at grandma's Well,
действительно у бабушки Ну
damn, I'm sitting here, there's a jacket. If you want a
блин тут сижу тут кофта есть Хочешь
jacket, I
кофту
'll show you grandpa's pants, not grandma's.
покажу есть дедушкины штаны не бабушкину
show
покажи
it might be Mom's and Babushkin's, what is
мамкина может быть а Бабушкина что ну
it really? Grandma's parents
что действительно Бабуш родители в
live in another house, they live in Neda's Well, no, this is
другом доме живут они Неде Ну нет это
Mom's thing, maybe Show me that
вещь мамы на может бы Покажи что
Babushkina's That's it, well,
Бабушкина Вот именно такое
Babushkin's other jacket Yes, it's a man's Well, I
Бабушкина Да это мужская А ну Одень я
'll see if it's a man's or grandma's dress Well
посмотрю или это мужская или бабушки Ну
can wear it,
может одевать ну
well, just throw it on your shoulders, I’ll see
накинь просто накинь на плечи я посмотрю
how
как
she does, you don’t have to, too, don’t force me,
она это не надо тоже меня не надо
your little girl lives there, in short, with you,
твоя денка там жит короче с тобой
no, I don’t have a girlfriend, Well  kid
ти Нет у меня нет девушки Ну пацан
So I don’t know your sweaters,
Значит я не знаю твои кофты
it means how you go into government services,
значит как ты захожу в госуслуги
look at the documents in front of you, you see I’m leafing through
документы смотри при тебе видишь листаю
a hundred not screenshots like personal documents,
сто не скрины типа личные документы
I go in like
захожу
this Labor is needed or what do you need or a
так Трудовая нужна или что тебе надо или
diploma or Labor diploma is what you need
диплом или Трудовая диплом что тебе надо
Labor
Трудовая
so work and pension So here it is
так работа и пенсия Значит вот сюда
should
надо
load And wait, look and Tell me how
грузит А подожди смотри а Расскажи как
you are How are you doing at school Here you are, you've been
ты Как тебе в школе Вот ты пришёл тебе
discharged This was your first job
выписали Это была твоя первая работа
Yes official No I worked back in
Да официальная Нет я работал ещё в
seventh grade At school Well,
седьмом классе В школе Ну
like, look, it turns out that I
типа могла бы смотри получается трудовую
did work then for the first time in the STM year 2016,
сделал тогда впервые в СТМ году 2016 год
we were arranged with schoolchildren officially,
нас устраивали у школьников официально
we were like general workers How
мы были как разнорабочие Сколько тебе
old were you in the seventh grade, you
лет в седьмом классе было тебе даже 14
weren’t even 14 14 Well, 14 years it was weeks, we
не было 14 Ну 14 лет это было недели мы
work in general  so come on, you came
работа общем вот давай так ты пришёл
when you went to school Yes, you were hired,
Когда в в школу Да тебя взяли на работу
electronic work book I see, I see
электронная трудовая книжка Вижу вижу
what they did, what did they do with
что что сделали А что сделали с бумажное
your paper work book when you  adj to
твоей трудовой книжкой когда ты прил в
school In the sense that they wrote down a record of what they
школу В смысле записали запись то что
gave you, yes, because the electronic work
отдали тебе да потому что электронном
book consists of an electronic
книга
work book, upon dismissal, in any case,
Трудовая при увольнении в любом случае
of course, they will write it down Well, according to
конечно будут записывать Ну по
provision, that is, in any case,
предоставлению то есть в любом случае
now an electronic work book is kept, I
сейчас ведётся электронная трудовая
don’t know Well, somehow you didn’t  you look
книжка не знаю Ну как-то ты не выглядишь
neither like a Fizruk nor like a dude who lives
ни как Физрук ни как чувак который живёт
with his grandmother, it’s somehow funny he lives with his grandmother,
с бабушкой както смешно жит с бабушкой
maybe I’ll say it again, I
сме может сме е раз говорю я 2 недели
’ve been here for 2 weeks now, I don’t care
нахожусь сейчас здесь как бы мне по
I'm having a blast I'm here at my grandmother's place of residence Well,
кайфу Я у бабушки здесь по прописке Ну и
you don't really look like a physical education teacher
на физрука ты не совсем
Why are you so tall? meter 84 T
похож Почему какой тебя рост метр 84 Т
Not enough for a
Маловато для
physical education teacher Why I'm not big enough at all The
физрука Почему Маловато у меня вообще
physical education teacher was meter 76 Well, because there's
Физрук был метр 76 Ну так потому что
a shortage of physical education teachers, some people took
нехватка физруков какие-то брали
strange
непонятных
pellets, in principle, there's a shortage of teachers  throughout the
катышек в принципе нехватка учителей по
country, not only physical education teachers And this is the
стране не только физруков А это рост
average height, my height is
среднестатистический у меня рост
normal and my weight is Well, you
нормальный а вес Ну ты какой-то ты вес
don’t want any weight  to offend, but somehow kind of fat
не хочу обидеть но как-то вроде жирный
No, actually no, I'm sitting there, is there any weight
Нет на самом деле нет я се ли вес есть
anyway? No, no.
по-любому
How much do you weigh
нету уже нету Сколько ты весишь
80 at a meter of 8480 But this is
80 при метр 8480 Но это
a boar No, if you correctly understood
кабан Нет если бы ты правильно понимал
what the ratio of height to weight at a meter is
что такое соотношение рост вес при метр
84 I should weigh  84 kg
84 я должен весить 84 кг
Look, first of all, I see your cheeks like this.
Смотри Я во-первых я вижу твои щёки так
Well, they have a
Ну они имеют
rather convex
довольно выпуклую
roundness. Well, that is, you, well, it’s kind of
округлость Ну то есть ты ну как бы
impossible to be here with normal abs, you
невозможно быть тут с нормальным прессом
know. Well, here they are  cheeks Well, you can’t
знаешь Ну тут такие щёки Ну нельзя так
do that Man, are you crazy about where the fat one is? Well,
Чел ты угараешь где здесь толстый Ну
show me
покажи
the abs
пресс
where you cut so that
где режи
I’m fat, here’s your
чтобы Я толстый бы вот тебе
profile, take it like that, well, it’s not
профиль возьми его так жмякни ну не то
what you mean. Well, yes, there’s
что ты имеешь в виду Вот это да тут есть
a little bit here, well, what kind of
немножко ну какой
physical education did I have at school? Fizruk Listen
физру у меня в школе был Физрук Слушай
dude, when he took off his T-shirt, you know,
чувак он когда снимал футболку знаешь
there was an eleventh-grader, ours just
там одиннадцатиклассница наши просто
squealed with boiling water, like, yes, he jumped out onto
пищали кипятком типа да он выскакивал на
the horizontal bar from the rivets, lifting, coup  If
турник с клёпок подъём переворот Если бы
you came out like that. In short, at our school,
ты вот так вышел У нас в школе
well, at least you have enough
короче ну как минимум хватает знаешь
authority, you know, there is enough authority among the children and I’m
авторитета хватает среди детей и работаю
already working. Well, you can for the lower grades. Yes,
уже а Ну ты может для младших классов Да
well, I’m the class teacher of the ninth grade. And I
ну я классный руководитель девятого А
work from the seventh to the eleventh. Well,
работаю с седьмого по одиннадцатый Ну
the eleventh, I think there you can already
одиннадцатый я думаю там тебе уже могут
Shchelbany push like guys there are
щелбаны надавать типа ребята там есть
really
правда
who Well, if you take a couple, there are those
кто Ну если брать парочку есть такие
who are stronger than me, well, because they are
которые сильнее меня ну потому что они
candidate masters of sports already in martial
кандидаты мастера спорта уже по боевым
arts, of course they can, we have a difference with
искусством конечно могут у нас разница с
them of 4 years 45 years you
ними 4 года 45 лет ты
What sport are you an expert in I am a football player  the
По какому спорту специалист я футболист
goalkeeper of
я вратарь
chickpeas thought if the striker would still
нуты думал если бы нападающий ещё бы
run away from them And so Rish You
убежать от нех А так Риш Ты только
will only receive cans from them
будешь получать банки от них
Well, I haven’t
Да ну я 2 года уже не
played for me for 2 years. If you didn’t notice, there’s
играю у меня Если не заметил вот на чаке
a little Kok on the chuck, it’s a Carnot hemangioma And
есть немножко Кок это Карно гемангиома А
I thought it was just a shadow Falling like that
я думал просто тень Падает так на мяч
hit the ball No, it’s congenital from the mother,
попал Нет это врождённая от мамы
passed on to 20 operations, but I’ll take that
передалась на 20 операций было а Прим ту
for a
за
school, not in the sense of the type Why the
школа не в смысле типа Почему не
unsuccessful type there is why the goalkeeper is
удавшийся типа там это почему вратарь
exactly that and oh so as not  I ran, it affected
именно то а о чтоб не бегал это повлияло
a lot of things, not only that I didn’t run, I
на многое не не то что не бегал я я
was first a fielder on the right side, but
сначала полевым был правый полу Ноза
because I had operations every 2 months from 14 to 17 years old,
того что мне с 14 по 17 лет каждые 2
I didn’t have time to
месяца операции делали я не успел
recover. And so, what are
восстанавливаться А так А чем тут
you talking about here,
общаешься
and in general, I communicate so easily on any
да вообще так просто общаюсь на любые
topic  absolutely make fun of me
темы абсолютно поприкалываться по меня
so that you choose Ukraine on purpose
по чтобы а Украину выбираешь специально
by the way No, I’m just standing
кстати Нет у меня просто стоит
Randomly they come across not only from
Рандом попадаются не только с
Ukraine Why do you think Russia
Украины А как думаешь Зачем Россия
attacked
напала на
Ukraine Yes, it’s their business
Украину Да их дело
in general how people are killed in our country  Ukraine
вообще как людей убивают у нас в Украине
Let you be eleventh graders In short, you
Пусть теб одиннадцатиклассники Короче
know, there’s like a director passing by.
знаешь там типа проходит директори
Well, it happened that it wasn’t to you and you
Ну а Бывало такое что не к тебе и ты там
lowered your eyes like things looked like in
опускал глаза типа дел вид что
short there were moments the first year of work at the
короче были моменты первый год работы по
beginning they were stupid Neya, but if you
началу были залупа Нея но если правильно
leave yourself right,
себя оставишь
moments like this won’t happen
моментов не произойдёт
you can Be  weaker than your
таких ты можешь Быть слабее своего
student But if you
ученика Но если ты правильно себя
set your character correctly, then nothing
поставишь характер свой то ничего не
will happen it happened after all it happened it happened Okay
произойдёт было такое всё-таки произошло
I turned my eyes away
Ладно глаза отвернул
right away never
сразу не ни разу не
was anything I can
было чем угодно могу
sing there were moments such that also  when
поть были моменты такие что также когда
I had moments with my
у меня моменты происходили с моим
curator when I was studying he, too, he is
куратором когда Я учился он тоже он
generally shorter than me and thinner than me
вообще ниже меня и худее меня
and I love the weak
и полюбому сла
who waves his arms strongly the one who is smarter
кто руками машет сильно тот кто умнее
the one who will
тот кто
properly discipline his Pony of the
правильно дисциплину наладит свою Поня
team Well Well, look at me somehow well,
коллективе Ну Ну смотри я как-то вот ну
damn me  In general, I myself am a psychologist by training.
блин я ж я вообще Сам по образованию
Yes, I have
психолог Да у меня психологической
18 years of experience in psychology and I can see
практики 18 лет работы и я блин вижу
when a person starts to play around. When I
когда человек начинает юлить Я когда
asked or there were situations, you immediately
спросил или бывали ситуации ты сразу
start to look away, get distracted there,
начи отводить глаза там отвлекаться Там
and so on.  I’m just saying again,
и так далее не просто я ещ раз говорю
firstly, they write to me And that’s
во-первых мне пишут И вот именно писать
exactly what they started writing to me, and secondly, I didn’t have
начали именно в во-вторых у меня не было
anything like that, you can think whatever you want,
такого ты можешь думать как хочешь ты
at least you’re already a bad psychologist,
как минимум ты уже плохой психолог так
since you immediately started to
как ты начал сразу начинать мне
prove to me that you doubt it  Am
доказывать то что типа там сомневаешься
I a teacher or not a teacher? A physical education teacher is not
учитель я или не учитель Физрук не
a physical education teacher.
Физрук Угу показать
Yeah, show a work psychologist. Well, a
трудовую психолог получается Ну да
good psychologist would probably not be at home,
хороший психолог наверное бы не домахи
Asya, but would make sure that you fulfill
Ася а бы сделал так чтобы ты исполнял
it,
его
uh, let’s say, orders go there Show your
ээ скажем заказы там пойди Покажи там
grandmother’s clothes there Show your abs That
одежду бабушки Покажи пресс Вот это был
would be a good psychologist  you can
бы хороший психолог ты можешь за это
get hooked on this absolutely unconditionally, but then you
зацепиться вообще безусловно но тут же ж
understand that the
понимаешь
factor at work is that if
работает фактор того что если бы как
you had behaved at least appropriately,
минимум подобающе бы ты себя
this would not have happened in the first place
вёл этого бы не произошло изначально
correctly, I don’t know, I don’t think so.  I
правильно не знаю не Мне кажется вот
know Or he went to work as a physical education teacher He
не знаю Или он пошл физруком работать Он
studied, like, in this
учился типа в этом
physical education school And where exactly did he
физкультурном А где именно
study in Krasnodar Well, it’s clear
учился в Краснодаре Ну понятно
that there are only two universities where he studies to become a
дело всего два ВУЗа где учится на
physical education teacher. I don’t know the name of the university, in short,
физруков Я не знаю название ВУЗа короче
I didn’t study in  Krasnodar now I can
Я учился не в Краснодаре сейчас я могу
see where you studied
посмотреть а где учился ты
I studied at KubSU I just realized there are
Я учился в КубГУ только понял есть
branches I studied in Slans on Kuban I understood the
филиалы Я в сланс на кубане учился понял
branch I had this one in the messenger He
отделение меня был этот в мессенджере Он
wrote to me we don’t communicate with him after the
мне писал мы с ним не общаемся после
start of these special operations in Valera
начала этих спецопераций во Валера
Finko,
финько
we’ve known each other on VKontakte for a long time  already
знакомый ВКонтакте мы ещё давно уже
know each other Well, yes, it’s
знакомы Ну да это
me, what do you mean, it’s you,
я что значит это ты
you, too, I didn’t understand what it reads from you
ты тоже не я понял то что у тебя
Yes, I understood that, it’s
считывает Да это я понял
cool. Think about how you have a friend who studied with you
прикольно Прикинь как ты у тебя друг
in Krasnodar, and here I am  I’m also saying this at the moment
учился в Краснодаре а тут я ещё моменте
that I wasn’t a great student at school.
говорю такое что я не в красе учился
Damn, what about me?
капец Да блин а мне
I studied in Slavyansk, I studied at
вообще Я учился в Славянске учился в
KubSU Yes, but in
КубГУ Да но в
the branch, of course, I look at your photos.
филиале фотографии конечно смотрю твои
But what do you think?
Но что как
Did you lose weight not so long ago? Yes, it used to be
не так давно скидывал вес да Раньше было
somehow more
как-то побольше
yes  On the contrary, at first I didn’t have enough I
да Наоборот я сначала мне не хватало Я
always dreamed of
всегда мечтал
typing and in the summer of twenty-two I
набрать и летом двадцать второго года
started typing
набирать начал
well, I got 85 87 even these are photos
хорошо набрал 85 87 даже это фотки
Probably from the summer of the second some of them
Наверно с лета д второго какие-то они
Which one are you talking about Well  where the
Какая именно ты про какую Ну там где
belly hangs a little, no, seriously
живот свисает немножко не ну серьёзно
About which one Yes, I’m seriously saying
Про какую именно Да я серьёзно говорю
this with
вот это
my hand Dude, you’re
рукой Чувак ты
right
точно
Let the dude tell me that I’m a
Давай чувак мне будет рассказывать что я
bad psychologist Yes, when I forced him to
плохой психолог Да когда я его заставил
bring grandma’s things to bring the abs to show
бабушкины вещи принести пресс показать
turn around the ball fold
повернуться шаровую складку
Yash Hello ZTE Hello and you  a
ужа Яш Здрав ЗТЕ Здравствуйте а вы
real person No, this is artificial
реальный человек Нет это искусственный
intelligence oh Thank God that you at least
интеллект ой Слава Богу что вы хотя бы
answer Where you come
отвечаете Вы
from I’m from Russia and the police can see
откуда Я из России а полицю видно А
what city Neftekamsk is Cool
город какой город Нефтекамск Прикольно
It’s on oil and  Kame Yes oil Kama how do
Это на нефти и Каме Да нефть Кама откуда
you know the origin of the city? My
вы знаете происхождение города у меня
father is from Cheboksary And my mother is from Naberezhnye
отец из Чебоксар А мама из Набережных
Chelny oh Naberezhnye Chelny is our favorite
Челнов ой Набережные Челны наш любимый
city,
город
but I myself come from Rostov, it turns out they
но сам я родом из Ростова они получается
studied there already during the Union and stayed to
там уже при Союзе учились и там остались
work there. I was born there but have been living there for 18 years.
работать Я родился там но уже 18 лет
in London in 2 years it will be the
живу в Лондоне через 2 года будет
twentieth You have a
двадцатое У вас
good black one, that’s how you work
хорошая чёрная вот как вы кем работаете
in Neftekamsk I worked in Neftekamsk
в Нефтекамске Я в Нефтекамске
damn it now you don’t
работал блин это сейчас вы не
write it down exactly
записываете точно
I had  my real estate agency
у меня было агентство недвижимости своё
And what
А что
was it? Well, I sold it, I went to
было Ну я его продал уехал в
Crimea, and to Crimea, not to
Крым а и в Крым не в
Krasnodar, we made anti-tank
Краснодар мы там делали противотанковые
barriers lines there, so I went to Crimea. So
заград линии поэтому поехал в Крым Так
what kind of anti-tank
вы какие противотанковые
lines
линии
are you in Sevastopol and he tells me Elnur
ме Севастополь и он мне говорит Эльнур
Yes, come I say I won the tender From the
Да приезжай Я говорит выиграл тендер От
Ministry  defense says we will
Министерства обороны говорит будем
make a barrier line I say we will organize everything well
делать заград линию Я говорю всё хорошо
That’s it in a nutshell And what are you
организуем Вот это вкратце А вы чем
doing I am a
занимаетесь Я преподаватель
university teacher And what department of
университета А какой факультет
anthropology do I teach at the department of
антропологии преподаю на кафедре
anthropology and the department of anthropology I
антропологии а кафедра антропологии я
applied mathematician this is discrete
прикладной математик это там дискретная
mathematics graphs of some kind discrete
математика графы какие-то дискрет
mathematics machei analysis combinatorics
математика мачей анализ комбинаторика
mathematical statistics well all this is
математическая статистика вот ну всё это
something very distant for me I
это что-то для меня очень далёкое я вот
heard about it so distantly Well
так отдалённо слышал об этом Ну у меня
anthropology is also far from me I understand
антропология тоже далеко от меня понял
Interesting but let’s
Интересно а вот Давайте
try  it’s interesting when you meet a
попробуем вот интересно когда встречаешь
person from another field. Let me give you
человека из другой сферы Давайте я вам
some interesting question on
буду какой-то интересный вопрос по
anthropology, not difficult, and you tell me about this
антропологии несложный а вы мне по вот
applied mathematics of yours.  Pobu Can a
исн математика прикладна побу Может ли
person from another sphere guess Okay,
человек из другой сферы угадать Хорошо
let's
давайте
uh, only with simple questions, only with
ээ только с простых вопросов только с
simple ones, only with simple ones Yes yes yes With
простых только с простых Да да да С
simple ones, what anthropology studies Well, the
простых что изучает антропология Ну
origin of man I think no, not
происхождение человека Я думаю нет не
the origin, origin is evolution, it
происхождение происхождение это эволюция
studies the types of people, yes, that is, uh, roughly
изучает типажи людей да то есть ээ грубо
speaking, so  biologically the breeds of people Yeah, I
говоря так биологически породы людей Ага
got it Okay, now let's you Well, I've already
понял О'кей Давайте теперь вы Ну я уже
lost honestly not Well, let's
проигрался честно не Ну давайте Вы
now you have some simple question about
теперь какой-то вопрос несложный по вот
this math of yours,
этой своей
okay 2 + 2 x 2 well there
хорошо 2 + 2 x 2 ну сть
will be I didn't talk about brackets if  the
будет Я же про скобки не говорил если
brackets just didn’t say then at first
скобки как раз не говорили тогда сначала
multiplication everything is
умножение всё
clear Yes, you’re handsome,
чётко Да вы красавчик
well done. Cool And you’re definitely a mathematician
молодец Прикольно А Вы точно математик
yes yes understood
да да понял
well the second in anthropology
хорошо второй по антропологии
uh Who are
эээ Кто такие
andropharm anro is a person Yes anro
андрофарм анро - это человек Да анро
Andra That is, anro is an
Андра То есть анро - это вот
anthropological anthropomorphic Yes that’s
антропологический антропоморфный Да вот
all  man Antra and phagus phagus is to
это это всё человек Антра а фаги фагус -
eat andropharm
это поедать андрофарм
rodo By the way, I described that they lived on
родо Кстати описва что жили они на
the territory of the modern Moscow
территории кстати современной Московской
region, by the way. This is  Ivanovskaya taco Well,
области Вот это Ивановской тако Ну
before there were no such areas in these
раньше не было таких областей на этих
territories, oh, let’s give you your second question.
территориях ой Давайте ваш вопрос второй
Listen, I’m not prepared. Well, let’s.
Слушайте я не подготовился Ну ну давайте
Well, Kato in mathematics
Ну Като по математике
can be something so simple, I’m an anthropologist, I’m
можно-то такой простой я антрополог я
interested, or I’ll guess,
интересно или угадаю
but only this without formulas should be
но только это без формул должно быть
correct
правильно
Yes, purely here  logic Well, it’s possible and I
Да чисто вот на логику Ну можно и с
don’t know with formulas Or there are definitions there I
формулами не знаю Или там определени
remembered I remembered Good question You
вспомнил вспомнил Хороший вопрос Вы
are participating in a competition and overtake the
участвуете в соревнования да обгоняй
second person who is running in second
второго человека который бежит вторым
place what place are you running Well if you
местом каким местом вы бежите Ну если вы
overtook the second one you are second,
обогнали второго вы стали вторым вот
well done you  very educated young
молодец Вы очень образованный молодой
man, I have respect for you, it’s
человек я к вам уважением отношусь
cool, you’re cool, let’s have a third
прикольно вы прик Давайте третий
question, damn it
вопрос
Yes, who are hydrocephalus in anthropology?
ээ Кто такие гидроцефалы в антропологии
the head is larger than the rest, the
есть голова больше чем у остальных не
head is not larger, but there is more water in the head than
голова больше а воды в голове больше чем
other fluids. For example, there are
у остальных жидкостей Вот например есть
populations that have more gray
популяции у которых больше серого
matter, so there are populations that have
вещества так есть популяции у которых
more water, exactly that  there is a
больше воды именно то есть в остатке
dry dry residue of the brain left, much
сухой сухой остаток мозга намного
less Clear And this influences in
меньше Понятно А это это влияет по
your opinion influences the
вашему мнению влияет влияет на
mental yes well it is not we are not
умственную да ну это Это не мы не
anthropologists already studying the influence of
антропологи уже изучаем влияние
the mental Yes we do typification yes And
умственное Да мы типизацию делаем да А
others there are uh these people who study the
другие есть э эти люди которые исследуют
cognitive abilities of a person So  they
когнитивные способности человека Так они
already prove that it influences but influences
уже доказывают что влияет но влияет
Let's your question sho
Давайте ваш вопрос шо
question What part of the brain influences No,
вопрос Какая часть мозга влияет на Нет
let's do math But I'm interested in
давайте по математике Но мне интересно
this math no no Let's do
это математика нет нет Давайте по
math well That was Okay let's have
математике ну Вот были Хорошо давайте
another
другой
question on logic Let's Mathematics is
вопрос на логику Давайте Математика это
logic
есть логика
Let's  In 2004, I, as a member of the Gru
Давайте в 2004 году я как участник Гру
team What Where When which was called
команды Что Где Когда которая называлась
pa, met in
па встретились в
Izhevsk Mr.
Ижевске господином
hmm asked the question 20 student teams,
гмм зали вопро 20 команд
only two teams answered this question This is the
только две команды Это команда
computer team and the parallelepiped team This is
компьютера и команда параллелепипед Это
my
моя
team the question seems to be not in the knowledge of
команда вопрос как бы не в знаниях
history It’s just logic That  there is this is not a
истории Тут прямо логика То есть это не
math question This is not Mathematics this is
по математике вопрос Это не Математика
gi mathematics practical logs there is
это ги математика практиче логи есть
mathematics let me not answer this question
математика давайте я на этот вопрос не
answered
ответил ответил
As they
Как
say my  commands, I’m
говорится моей команды я вот это всё
telling you all this so that you understand
этом рассказываю чтобы вы понимали то
that there is no need for the complexity of the question, but the
что не надо сложность вопроса да
complexity of the questions is nougat word question is a very
сложность вопросов нугу сло вопро очень
difficult question 18 teams did not
сложный вопрос 18 команд не
answer 18 Did not answer and two answered
ответило 18 Не ответило а две ответило
Yes 18 did not answer two answered This is
Да 18 не ответила две ответила Это
a computer and a parallelepiped is cool So
компьютера и паралелепипед прикольно Так
you can do it  check the newspaper
вы можете это проверить газете
the antenna in Izhevsk is still there Let's
антенна в Ижевске всё-таки там Давайте
look well this is generally a cool
да смотри хорошо это вообще классный
question I'll tell you this in the sixties
вопрос я вам так скажу в шестидесятых
Great Britain conducted a survey What
годах Великобритания проводили опрос Что
is the most famous
является самым знаменитым
watercraft  Name the most famous
плавсредство Назовите самое знаменитое
watercraft
плавсредство
according to this survey, well, the Titanic is
по данному опросу ну Титаник
too easy to hike Well, either the Titanic
походу слишком легко Ну либо Титаник
or, logically,
либо логично же
the titanium everyone answered Titanic Wait Stop
титани все ответили Титаник Подожди Стоп
stop stop then now wait oh well
стоп стоп тогда сейчас подожди а ну Ещё
Repeat again I won’t tell you the answer I’ll
раз повторите я не буду ответ говорить я
give you 4 minutes meh Let’s
вам дам 4 минуты ме Давай е ещё раз
try again  then if not tita and the
попробуем тогда если не тита да бы
titanic it would be easy for for such a League
Титаник было бы легко для для такой Лиги
this is you would have Great Britain
это Это у вас бы Великобритания
imagine me Imagine me again the
представляете я Представьте я ещё раз
sixties
шестидесятые года
Great Britain  opinion poll the most famous
Великобритания соцопрос самые знаменитые
floats in the
плав в
means in your opinion
средства по вашему мнению
in the sixties Yes, that in the
в шестидесятых годах Да именно что в
sixties this is the Key Dasha of the
шестидесятых годах это Ключевое Даше
year so post-war
года так послевоенная
Europe Great
Европа
Britain that
Великобритания та
Yes, someone tells you yes no damn it,
Да тебе подсказывает кто-то да нет блин
you're handsome out of 18 teams answered
ну ты красавчик из 18 команд ответила
only
только
two parallelepipeds and a
две параллелепипед и компьютера
pair of computers  Well, listen to the whole
пара Ну слушай всю
coma, then I think this is for You, it’s not
кома я потом думаю это для У вас же не
some kind of serious
школьный чемпионат какой-то серьёзный
All-Russian school championship, then for the Titanic it would be
Всероссийский то для Титаника это было
Easy means something yes yes  Yes, damn
бы Изи значит что-то да дада да блин
it, there are so many people I haven’t asked the question
мо я вот сколько людям не задавал вопрос
I would, to be honest, I would
я бы если честно я бы на этот вопрос
never answer this question in my life why Well,
никогда в жизни не ответил почему Ну
because I wouldn’t answer I always told the truth
потому что я бы не ответил Я правду себе
to my face, it’s
в лицо всегда
cool Let’s have one more question, I’ll
прикольно Давайте ещё один вопрос я
fail miserably and many times  oty Okay,
проиграю с треском да множ оты Хорошо
let’s ask a question, just let’s say that it’s logic
давайте вопрос толь давайте что логики
because anthropology And for logic,
потому что антропология А на логику
well, you want a question for logic, yes,
хорошо хотите вопрос на логику да
let’s
давайте
let’s write it down or it’s possible
давайте можно записывать или можно можно
Well, look, I didn’t write it down. I heard it by ear. Well, you
Ну смотри я ж не записывал Я на слух Ну
can. Let’s write it down. Yes, there will be
може Давайте записывать Да по тамм будут
key questions. So  it
ключевые вопросы Так
means the boy Ildar from
значит мальчик Ильдар из
Neftekamsk sold his property and went to the
Нефтекамска продал сво имущество ехал в
Russian-occupied Crimea.
оккупированный Россией Крым
Yeah. A few years later, the Armed Forces of
Угу Через несколько лет Вооружённые силы
Ukraine, with the support of NATO, began the
Украины при поддержке НАТО начали
procedure for the liberation of Crimea and its
процедуру освобождения Крыма и его
demilitarization.
демилитаризации
parallelepiped like this Can I have
параллелепипед так А можно наводящий
another leading question?
вопрос ещё
Let’s do it Ildar Yes Ildar let’s do it like this
Давайте Ильдар Да Ильдар давайте так
Ildar
Ильдар
uh  Ildar had and write Ildar
ээ у Ильдара было и напишите у Ильдара
had X of these rubles, dollars Let's have
было X этих рублей долларов Давайте
dollars, we'll have dollars in the summer Yes, he
долларов мы будем доллара лете Да он
went to Crimea and invested there and
поехал в Крым и инвестировал там и
dollars Uh-huh
долларов Угу
Yes, Ildar had only a few years left to live on
Да на жизнь Ильдару оставалось
And short And short there was a
крат не И краткая И краткая оставалось
question Read a three-letter word that
вопрос Прочитайте слово из трёх букв что
will remain  from Ildar after the de-occupation of
останется у Ильдара после деоккупации
Crimea so
Крыма так
yours in short Neftikamsk from our
твой короче Нефтикамск с нашего
Ukrainian Crimea
украинского Крыма
Come on
Давай
beach Eldar Eldar damn cool
пляжа Эльдар Эльдар блин прикольный
Battle  it turned out
Баттл получился
Hello Hello, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsy,
хмельниц Вы
where are you from Krasnodar, I understand, look, I
откуда с Краснодара понял вот смотрите Я
read the news that in Russia there is some kind of
читал новости что в России там какой-то
excitement with eggs now, why do you have
ажиотаж с яйцами сейчас почему у вас
eggs in
яйца в
Krasnodar Yes, you know, I haven’t taken them for a long time,
Краснодаре Да вы знаете давно не брала
somehow I didn’t even delve into the cost, you live
как-то даже не вникал в стоимость живёте
without  eggs Well, I’m coping for now. Cool,
без яиц Ну пока справляюсь Прикольно да
yes, what do you have in your
а что у вас в
diet? Do you know that I work at school
рационе в рационе А вы знаете я в школе
from morning until evening and I eat at
работаю с утра и до вечера питаюсь в
school and you  eat school, I
школе а вы едите шко
understand, that is, And until what time in the evening do you
понял то есть А до скольки вечера вы
sit at
сидите в
school? Well, I work in two shifts now.
школе Ну я в две смены работаю сейчас
Therefore, from 8:00 in the morning until 6:00 in the evening,
Поэтому вот с 8:00 утра и до 6:00 вечера
how is it in two shifts, the teacher is
а как это в две смены учительница это
like Well, then, the official duties are
как Ну так служебные обязанности
substituting And your salary
замещение А зарплату вам в двойную
they pay double for
платят за
it, well, for replacement Of course they pay extra,
это ну за замену Конечно же доплачивают
yes no, is it a replacement or do you
да нет так это замена или это вы
work regularly so no no no not
регулярно работаете так нет нет нет не
regularly Well, that’s just how
регулярно Ну просто вот в последнее
things have happened lately Well, lately
время так сложилось Ну в последнее время
it’s how many months a day Well  about
это сколько месяц день Ну где-то недели
two weeks this is no longer a replacement it’s already on a
две это уже не замена это уже на
regular
регулярной
basis Well, so far it’s turned out like that, well,
основе Ну пока так вышло да ну со
next week it won’t be like that anymore xo
следующей неделе уже так не будет хо
Okay 2 weeks ago when did you
Окей 2 недели назад вы когда во сколько
come home from school at what time? Yes, you
приходили домой тогда со школы Да вы
know in different ways
знаете по-разному
how things turned out  Well, at three o’clock
как как складывалось ну часа в три вче
yesterday I’m home, so at home, like we
домой значит э дома типа
had dinner No, basically I
ужинали Нет в основном доставку
order delivery, like Yeah, well, without eggs,
заказываю доставку типа Ага ну без яиц
like yeah Well, yeah And somehow I’m getting along
типа да Ну да А как-то обхожусь
cool cool How much now Maybe
прикольно классно А сколько сейчас Может
you have a girlfriend There’s some, maybe
у вас подружка Есть какая-то может
you’ll find out  How much are eggs now in
узнаете Почём яйца сейчас в
Krasnodar, I see you’re just so
Краснодаре я смотрю вас прям так
interested, I saw that there are queues for
заинтересовала я видел что очереди за
eggs there in Belgorod, for example, there are still
яйцами там в Белгороде например там ещё
such things Yes, such cases probably
Да ну такие Да случаи такие наверное
happen Well, I haven’t noticed that in the city I understand,
бывают Ну тако с городе я не замечала
that is, there are enough eggs in Krasnodar, I
Поня то есть в Краснодаре яиц
think so with eggs  there won’t be any problems, I
хватает думаю что да с яйцами проблем не
understand, I understand, and what are the problems
будет понял понял А с чем есть проблемы
with the products?
с продуктов
And yes, you know, we live relatively well.
А да вы знаете относительно хорошо живём
Well, at least judging by myself, there
Ну по крайней мере по себе сужу всего
is enough of everything in abundance. Everything is somehow
хватает всего в достатке Всё как-то
calm and smooth. Well, for example, what do you
спокойно ровно Ну чего например вам
have enough of, what products do you need?  I
хватает каких продуктов вам
have enough of all the basic technical equipment I need, what do
хватает да всех каких мне надо базовых
Russians eat? Well,
техе чем россияне питаются Ну у вас
maybe you have different products that are not the same as
может разные продукты не такие как у
ours, what do you mean, well, some
нас ну что вы имеете в виду ну какие-то
cereals,
крупы
meat, vegetables, fruits, absolutely everything is
мясо овощи фрукты абсолютно всё в
freely available at good normal
свободном доступе по хорошим нормальным
prices, but how much do
ценам а почём
cereals cost?  depending on what kind of
крупы крупы Ну смотря какая например
buckwheat, for example, what kind of buckwheat? Well, 85 rubles, when was the
Какая гречневая крупа Ну рублей 85 когда
last time you took it? And when was the
её последний раз брала А когда ты вы
last time you took river grain? It’s
последний раз брали речн крупу
been a long time, I see.  I’m telling you
давненько я вот видите Я же вам говорю
how I eat at school, I mostly eat here
как я ем в школе в основном питаюсь тут
eggs, I don’t know the eggs, I don’t know
яйца не знаю яйца не знаю не там
the delivery is not there. In short, I come home and
доставку Короче прихожу домой доставку
order delivery for myself. And how did I start
себе заказываю А как э начала
listing? Krupko, everything went right away
перечислять Крупко сразу сразу всё пошло
and I remembered the price Yes How much in the
и и цену вспомнила Да Сколько в
supermarket Well, yes Well, that’s when I took it  It’s
супермаркете Ну да Ну вот когда брала
not clear when I took it, but I remember that 85
брала непонятно когда но помню что 85
rubles, in short, I don’t know. I honestly say,
руб короче я вот не знаю Я честно говорю
I
я
won’t remember in my life, I probably know. How much the
в жизни не вспомню наверное знае Сколько
products I bought a month
стоили продукты которые я покупал месяц
ago cost. That’s it, yes. Well, you see, I just have a
назад Вот так да Ну видите у меня просто
memory like this, this is what I took  I
память такая раз вот что-то я брала
remembered a long time ago Uh-huh And so you
давно вспомнилось Угу А так вот Это вы
took this cereal a long time ago and everything else,
давно взяли эту крупу и всё остальное
just after getting it at school you eat it and delivery it at
только достав в школе жрёте и доставка в
school and delivery Yes And you said you eat
школе и доставка Да А вы сказали жрёте
it, you eat it Yes, well, that’s so youthful, not not
жрёте Да ну это так по молодёжному не не
ambassadors of you The rumor is good, it’s
послы вас Слух хороший это по
youthful Well, I  just a little to the
молодёжному так Ну я просто немножко к
younger generation that the slang is so
молодому поколени что сленг такой по
youthful No, it’s not youthful,
молодёжному Нет это не по молодёжному
it’s rude why Well, according to the youth, I
это по грубому почему Ну по молодёжному
eat, I eat, I eat  I'm at school, yeah Yeah, you're eating And you're a
ем ем ем я в школе да Угу едите А вы
primary school teacher and all this is the
чего начальных классов а всё это са
most correct teacher because
самые правильные учительница потому что
your children don't speak slang there yet,
они у вас ещё дети сленгом там не
I understand, that's why for you it's like that,
говорят я понял поэтому для вас это так
you're a little bit of that Yes, I understand Well,
вы немножко от этого Да я понял Ну вот
now
сейчас
in my desires  general now I’ll pick up
во желания ми общ сейчас Я подберу
an analogue Yes, I’m just used to it, it
аналог Да я просто привык посла го это
will be you were very amazed, so
будет вы были очень поражены вот так
amazed emotionally, like this, you know, yes, that’s
поражены эмоционально вот так знаете да
right, that’s good Yes, it’s very
вот это прямо вот хорошо Да очень
cool that your dictionary of synonyms
здорово что у вас словарь синонимов так
works so well Yes, for me  very
здорово срабатывает Да у меня очень
good synonymous base class And
хорошая синонимическая база класс А ну
well, I’m just used to it ul as a
просто я я просто при привык уль как
reader I give you a solid A as
вчитель ставлю вам твёрдую пятёрку как
someone Yak reader and because I hear you
кто Як вчителька а потому что я слышу Вы
said something a little in Ukrainian
что-то по-украински немножко сказали
Yeah you don’t need to speak Ukrainian
Ага не надо по-украински говорить
speak in s yay you need  you don’t prohibit it, it’s not
говорите на с яы надо вы не запрещай не
just, well, it’s unpleasant when they start in Russian
не просто ну неприятно когда Россия они
in Ukrainian.
по-украински
Why is that so and they They want to be
начинают А чего так а они Они хотят быть
like us, we don’t want that, what does it have to do with it, they
как мы мы не хотим чтобы Причём здесь
want it like we didn’t say  Well, they want to
хотят как мы не сказала бы ну они хотят
migrate there for us, you know, like the
там мигрировать под нас понимаете как
Ukrainians, we don’t want to, we want to share like this.
украинцы мы не хотим мы хотим вот так
You say to yourself there, so
поделиться Вот вы себе Говорите там так
we’re like that, oh well, well, you speak
мы так да ладно Ну вы же говорите сейчас
Russian now Well, now, yes, because I’m
на русском Ну сейчас да потому что я
talking now with the Russians. I need to talk to
говорю сейчас с россиянами Мне нужно с
them.  Like talking But I don’t want
ними Типа говорить А я не хочу чтобы
Russians to speak Ukrainian. You
россияне говорили по-украински Вот
see how interesting it turns out, you see, I
видите как интересно получается видите я
want to know two languages ​​so that Russians
хочу знать два языка россияне чтобы
know one,
знали один
and I understand Ukrainian well,
а я добро разумею украинскую
maybe I know how to spilk
возможно умею спилкування
now I  I’ll see the language right away yes yes no I ca
сейчас я поду сразу мову видня да да нет
n’t see the message right away yes Oh
не видня сразу посыла да Ой
synonymous row you need to choose your
синонимический ряд надо подобрать ваше
unique face Dava look how
уникальное лицо Дава вот смотрите как
cool Well wonderful Well how
здорово Ну прекрасно Ну до чего же
amazing Yes and Crimea those who live there I’ll
потрясающе Да а Крым тех кто там живёт Я
tell you this of those residents who
вам так скажу тех жителей кто там
live there And whose
живёт А чей
Krasnodar of those residents who live there,
Краснодар тех жителей которые там живут
that is, Krasnodar is not
то есть Краснодар - это не
Russia, it’s Russia Well, they live there
Россия это Россия Ну там же живут
Krasnodar wait Wait Wait Stop
Краснодар подожди Подождите Подожди Стоп
stop stop then Russia Krasnodar is what
стоп стоп то Росси Краснодар - это какая
country Krasnodar is located  in Russia but Krasnodar
страна Краснодар находится в России но
residents live in it Krasnodar And the
живут в нём краснодарцы Краснодар И
Russians rolled into one And you get You are from
россияне в одном лице А вы получа Вы
Krasnodar
краснодарка
yes Well how can I say I didn’t live exactly in
да Ну как сказать я жила не совсем в
Krasnodar Well let’s say yes And where you didn’t
Краснодаре Ну допустим да А где вы не
really live before well next to the suburb of
совсем жили раньше ну рядом пригород
Krasnodar
Краснодаром
what is it called it doesn’t matter important doesn’t matter
как называется это неважно важно неважно
important for  It’s important for me to understand who you were
важно для меня важно понять кто Вы были
when, before they became red, there was
когда до того как стали красно было
a small force next to Krasnodar. It’s
маленькое сило рядом с Краснодаром Это
completely unimportant.
совершенно неважно
You’re a girl from a
Вы поди поди семис ряд девушка из
downtrodden Russian village like this. Well, I wouldn’t
российской забитой деревни вот так Ну не
say that she’s from a downtrodden village.  Yes, because
сказала бы что из забитой Да потому что
Kuban Kubanka Yes, the hall with the Cossacks
Кубань кубанька Да зас заля с казаками
there are not crammed there, crammed into it in
там не забитые забитые в это в
all sorts of Yaroslavl regions Yes,
ярославских всяких областях Да
you are Russified and from the Russified
вы а обрусевший да из обру из обрусевший
once Cossack village and village Well,
когда-то казацкой деревни да села Ну
your vision is your vision
Ваше видение это ваше видение
yes And for what purpose are you communicating with
да А с какой целью вы общаетесь с
Russians Can I find out from you, I find
россиянами Можно у Вас узнать я нахожу
Oh, sorry nomis, I’ll pick up
Ой извините номис ий рядм подобрать
people with limited mental
людей с ограниченными умственными
abilities and low and low
способностями Да и низкой и низкой
social
социальной
responsibility  and I’m spending with him
ответственностью и провожу с ним
now, like this immediately
сейчас как это сразу
synonymous descent, I’m
синонимические спускание я в ихние уши в
pouring certain speeches into their ears into their ears Yes,
ихние в уши вливаю определённые речи Да
with the help of which I still think that
с помощью которых я всё-таки считаю что
some Oh, excuse me, a number of people with
некоторые Ой извините ческий ряд людей с
low
низкой
intellectual abilities with low
интеллектуальной с низкими
intellectual abilities, you
интеллектуальными способностями ничего с
can’t do anything with them  they will fly in and fly out
ними не сделаешь у них влетит и вылетит
and something will remain there. So I think that
а чтото там Отт остатся Вот я думаю что
you will have something
у вас что-то
left. Well, well,
останется Ну как Ну
listen, maybe, maybe you don’t
слушайте Возможно Возможно вы вы же не
look like a person with
похожи на Правда Ну на человека с
short hair, really?  intellectual
низкими интеллектуальными
abilities Well, I don’t know who you
способностями Ну я не знаю кого вы
mean by these, it doesn’t seem like you
имеете в виду под этими не похоже Вот вы
’re telling me that’s how I talked to you, you
мне кажете вот я так с вами пообщался вы
don’t get
не складывайте
the impression of people who are designated by
впечатление людей которые обозначаются
this name next to each other. Thank
этим чески рядом Благодарю
you, then Crimea is what kind of
вас то Крым - это какая
country is Russia at the moment? What does it
страна на данный момент Россия Что
mean on
значит на
at the moment it is
данный на данный момент она находится
under the rule of Russia, this is territory, then
под властью России это территория то
Russia occupied Crimea.
Россия оккупировала Крым
So, at the moment, this is Russian
Так ну на данный момент это Российская
territory. That’s all I can do because it’s
территория Это всё что я могу сза
occupied according to the laws of Russia, this is
оккупирована по законам России это
legal territory,
законная территория
that’s why I love it  Russian teachers for
за что я люблю российских учителей за то
being like this Oh, sorry, this is the Sinami
что они такие Ой извините это синами
row, people
ский ряд люди
with a heightened sense of fear,
с обострённой чувством страха
the agaves will
агавам так
like it so much Well, amazing,
понравится вывернули Ну потрясающе
listen Well,
слушайте Ну
amazingly
потрясающе
wonderful Well, okay, I’ll send you away Oh,
замечательно Ну хорошо всё пошлю вас Ой
excuse me, I’ll tell you in a seismic row,
извините скажу вам сейсмическим рядом
I’ll say goodbye to you, pretending that it
попрощаюсь с вами делая вид что
was nice talking to you
приятно с вами было пообщаться
Yes, you know, but I won’t pretend, I’ll
Да вы знаете а я не буду делать вид я
tell you straight I had a good time with you It’s
вам прямо скажу Мне было неплохо с вами
great to talk all the best to you,
Здорово пообщаться всего вам доброго
may you have peace and tranquility of your feet
пусть у вас будет мир спокойствие стоп
Long life to you  And what does it take for
Долгих вам для жи что А что нужно чтобы
us to have
у нас стал
peace, for you to have peace? What do you
мир чтобы у вас стал мир А вы как
think? Well, I think that the Russian
думаете Ну я думаю что э российские
occupiers should, oh, excuse me, withdraw
оккупанты должны Ой извините вывести
their troops from the territory of Ukraine.
свои войска с территории Украины
Well, this should be some kind of mutual
Ну это должен быть какой-то взаимный
process where people will begin to hear
процесс где люди начатся слышать друг
each other before even  just look, this is a mutual
друга до ещё раз смотрите вот взаимный
process, this is Russia withdrawing from the territory of
процесс это Россия выводит с территории
Ukraine and Ukraine withdrawing from the territory of
Украины и Украина выводит с территории
Ukraine, what is there no reciprocity, it’s just a
Украины в чём взаимность нет это просто
mutual process where people will learn to
взаимный процесс где люди научатся
hear each other and agree on
слышать друг друга и договариваться О
what to agree on  there is nothing to negotiate in the world,
чём договариваться во мире не о чём
look, we lived, we
договариваться смотрите мы жили мы от
didn’t want anything from Russia, Russia came and is
России ничего не хотели Россия пришла и
taking away our territories, what we
у нас забирает территории о чём мы
must agree on, here are your
должны договориться вот ваши
options for agreeing. Well, at least let’s say
варианты договориться Ну хотя бы скажем
the proposals that were at the
так те предложения которые были на
Istanbul negotiations, I think they are
стамбульский переговорах я их считаю
quite good. What proposals  were at the
вполне Здра Какие предложения были на
Istanbul
стамбульский
negotiations Well, let's just say these were
переговорах Ну скажем так это были
quite sensible
вполне здравые
proposals, please shake them. What proposals were there for the
ми предложения Какие предложения были на
Istanbul negotiations? Well, at least
стамбульские жения Ну по крайней мере
as far as I know, it was
насколько мне это известно было
proposed that Russia was even ready to
предложено что Россия была готова даже
withdraw its troops from  territory of Ukraine,
вывести свои войска с территории Украины
where are you in general, this is subject to the condition, if I’m not
где вы вообще это при условие если я не
mistaken, neutral status Where did you
ошибаюсь нейтрального статуса Где вы это
read all this, where can you read this, well, I
всё читали где можно почитать такое ну я
can’t give you a specific name right now, because
сейчас не могу вам назвать конкретно
somewhere there is no time
исто гдето вре
anywhere like this,
ни нигде нет так
nowhere
нигде
okay Sorry, the girl
ладной Извините девушка
who’s not quite telling
которая не совсем говорит
the truth, I’m not quite telling the truth  the truth Well, this is
правду не совсем говорю правду Ну это
your subjective opinion No, this is
ваше ваше субъективное мнение Нет это
objective if you are right, show me
объективное если прав покажите покажите
the essence, subjective no, not a single
сути субъектив никакие вот ни один
person who opens his mouth to me about the
человек который мне открывает рот про
Istanbul agreements can
стамбульские соглашения не может
show what kind of agreements these were,
показать какие же эти были соглашений
no one saw them like that  you are not
никто их не видел так а вы с ними не
fully acquainted with them, no one had
ознакомлены полностью так никто не было
any Istanbul agreements,
никаких стамбульский соглашений ни о чём
nothing was agreed upon,
не договорились не было
no, yes. Well, what if even your Budanov
нет да Ну как же если даже ваш Буданов
recently said that Zhenya, wait in
недавно говорил что Жени бы то подожди в
Istanbul, they agreed on something?
Стамбуле о чём-то
No, unfortunately, we didn’t
договорились Нет к сожалению не
agree, which means nothing  that means there
договорились значит никаких вот значит
were no agreements in
никаких договорённостей не было в
Istanbul,
стамбульский
yes, well, why were there proposals?
да Ну почему же предложение-то были
Wait, stop, there were no agreements,
Подождите стоп договорённостей
no negotiations, yes, nothing was agreed upon, there
ни не переговоры какие-то были Да ни о
were no agreements  Istanbul
договорённостей не было стамбульский
truth Well, they didn’t happen Yes,
правда Ну они не случились Да сорвались
they didn’t happen, they didn’t happen Yes, you have some kind of
они не случились да у вас есть какой-то
official document published by
документ официальный опубликованный
your RONO that your side proposed
вашей РОНО что ваша сторона предлагала
that we really If you
чтобы мы действительно Если вы так
say so, that we now
утверждаете чтобы мы сейчас это
talk about it Because it seems to me that
пообщались о этом Потому что мне кажется
you can look at it Yes  Well, look,
вы это можете посмотреть Да ну смотрите
one of the negotiators, he
один из переговорщиков он же давал
recently gave int not one of the Negotiators
недавно инте не один из Переговорщик
Look, not not one of the negotiators But
Смотри не не один из переговорщиков А
here is the document Well, if we are talking about these
вот документ Мы ж если мы говорим о этих
about documents and about an agreement, it’s not like
о документах да о договоренности Это не
someone  I was thinking something to myself, there is a
то что кто-то что-то себе думал вот есть
document, your country, for example, Lavrov or
документ ваша страна например Лавров или
whoever it is, or what else you have, yes it
кто там да Или какой ещё у васл есть да
shows, look, we offered this
показывает смотрите мы предлагали вот
Yes, we were
такое Да нас
sent that Russia proposed to leave
послали что предлагала Россия уйти из
Crimea and Donetsk Lugansk VOKH Yes, I would
Крыма и донецко Луганска ВОХ Да я бы
study this issue but you  now you are
изучила этот вопрос поп вы сейчас вы
now saying that Russia in Istanbul
сейчас говорите что Россия в Стамбуле
proposed that it would withdraw troops from
предлагала что она выведет войска с
Crimea, Donetsk and
Крыма Донецка и
Lugansk, these are specific points, I
Луганска конкретные вот эти пункты я вам
can’t tell you everything, I understood that is, you Oh,
не могу назвать всё понял то есть вы Ой
sorry, you just came up with this on  move
извините просто придумали это на ходу
No, I’m not making it up, you said, you said,
Нет я не придумаю вы сказали Вы сказали
you said with your mouth with your mouth that
Вы сказали своим ртом своим ртом что
Russia was ready to withdraw its troops in
Россия была готова вывести свои войска в
exchange for a neutral status. Well, if I’m not
обмен на нейтральный стату Ну если я не
mistaken. If based on
ошибаюсь Если основываться на мнении
your opinion, I understand correctly that Russia
вашего я правильно понимаю что Россия
was ready to withdraw troops from Crimea,
готова была вывести войска с Крыма
Donetsk and  Lugansk Yes, well, specifically from
Донецка и Луганска Да ну конкретно С
which territories I don’t know, but that is,
каких территорий Я не знаю а то есть всё
I understand everything Do you also have any questions for me
я понял Ещё у вас есть ко мне какие-то
or will he
вопросы или всё-таки уже убежит
finally run away? I’ll run away. But you ca
наконец-то Убегу А вам уже всё уже прямо
n’t stand it anymore  and I couldn’t help but
нени в терпёж и ни в моготу я уже
look at how you fell out with your Oh,
посмотрел как вы вывалились своей Ой
sorry, in your nonsense, I enjoyed it,
извините в своей брехнею насладился этим
my synonymic row simply can’t
мой мой синонимический ряд уже просто не
stand it anymore, it’s already exhausted itself No, it has
выдерживает он уже исчерпал себя Нет он
n’t exhausted it with me, it’s very rich
не исчерпал се у меня он очень богаты
isl No, it’s just emo that’s emotionally creeping in, not
исл Нет просто эмо эмоционально лезет не
this synonymic row  but just
этот синонимический ряд а просто
to explain to you What type of person are you, well, I mean,
объяснить вам Какая вы типа ну в смысле
this is a girl with how Then it’s correct to
это девушка с как Тогда правильно сино
say Sino Miski a girl with very, uh, stupid
миски сказать девушка с очень ээ глупыми
views on life Well, I understand you
воззрениями на жизнь Ну я вас поняла
Okay, listen, it's great that you could assert yourself very much during these
Ладно слушайте Здорово Что вы могли эти
10 minutes in your life.
10 минут в своей жизни по
Yes, I very much. To
самоутверждаться очень Да я очень очень
be honest, I assert myself and
Я честно говоря я самоутверждаются и
now you have helped me a lot to
сейчас Вы мне очень помогли
assert myself. I just know you. Well,
самоутвердиться Я просто знаете ва Ну
I'm glad to be useful to you. Of course,
что ж я рада быть Вам полезной Конечно
you are the first person today.  I am the
вы вы сегодня первое на ком я
first to assert myself, but you, I am your
самоутверждаются первоя по вы я у вас
first How cool, more precisely, you are my
первый Как здорово точнее вы у меня
first, I don’t know, I know you had such
первый я не знаю я у вас зна такая была
a warm-up Now you can no longer
разминка Сейчас вы уже можете себя не
restrain yourself, imagine now
сдерживать представляете сейчас
switch  of the synonymous series, that
переключитесь синонимического ряда то
is, it’s
есть
already interesting to listen to the success of the forces of
уже интересно слушайте успехов сил
health, all the best And to you, so that there are
здоровья всего доброго А вам чтоб
more Russian occupiers
побольше российских оккупантов
Andrei popk king of the synonymous series
Андрей попк король синонимических рядов
Hello Hello, city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from? I’m from Samara from
Хмельницкий Вы откуда Я из Самары из
Samara, you’re resting somewhere
Самары вы где-то отдыхаете
now, you’re not at home, but I think you have some kind of
сейчас нет дома а я думаю у вас какая-то
color music Maybe in a club somewhere there’s just no
цветомузыка Может в клубе где-то просто
sound, there’s no music, I think it’s me who
звука нет музыки думаю это я дома
turned on this little device at home, a ball
включила такой вот шарик приборчик шарик
Yes, a cool ball. Why did you decide that?
Да прикольный шарик А что вы так решили
in such a mood to do with the
се такой настроени сделать с
balloon, what again Why did you decide
шариком что ещё раз С чего вы решили
exactly such a mood here? What to
именно такое настроение здесь Что
turn on this balloon so that the light
включить шарик этот чтоб свет
And what did I decide, yes, I’m just scary
А что я так решила да просто я страшная
and decided to decorate myself with a balloon, yes,
и решила себя украсить шариком м да
self-critical, quite self-critical Yes, I
самокритично довольно самокритично Да
realized, I just feel like this today
понял просто мне уже сегодня вот так
they said how
сказали какая я
scary I am, I won’t say anything for now, I’m still
страшная я пока промолчу я пока ещё
forming your opinion. Let me do it. Let me
формирую мнение вас Давайте могу Давайте
help you. Whose Crimea do you think?
чтобы мне помочь Как вы считаете чей
Well, what about the Crimea of ​​the Crimeans? Oh now the eighth
Ну как че Крым крымчан О сейчас восьмой
time
раз
will be
будет
why? Well, what do we have?  such a dialogue will
почему Ну что же это у нас такой диалог
not
не
work out I look I thought I asked
сложится я я смотри я Задумался я задал
myself a question Why is she not scary and
себе вопрос А в чём она не страшная и
so I look and
вот смотрю и
think oh well scary not scary
думаю да ну и ладно страшная не страшно
what's the difference Okay I'm scary Well shchep
какая разница Хорошо я страшная Ну щей
Crimea that's good scary wait stop
Крым это же хорошо страшная подожди стоп
stop not good but bad  scary not
стоп не хорошо а плохо страшное не
good good scary this is still Be patient This is
хорошо хорошо страшное это ещё Терпи Это
bad scary really very scary So
плохо страшное реально очень стрёмно Так
where is excellent Well excellent - this is positive
где отлично Ну отлично - это позитивная
paint excellent good and here it’s
краска отлично хорошо а тут жесть
terrible terrible for example
страшное например
[music]
[музыка]
there for example if if you
там вот например если если вы
associated yourself with some scary
ассоциировали себя с каким-то страшным
animal with whom it would be
животным с кем это было
no Let's cover No let's wait
бы нет Давайте покры Нет давайте подожди
again smo if not then I
по ещё раз смо вот если нет так я же
heard your answer I'm not
услышал ваш ответ я же мне это не
interested in politics I don't talk about politics at all
интересно политика Я вообще политике не
here I'm just talking to people  life
общаюсь тут я просто с людьми о жизни
there about Excellent You don’t communicate in common And I
там о Отлично Вы не обща поли А вообще
don’t communicate at all I’m not interested She’s tired
не общаюсь мне не интересно Она надоела
I ask people, for example,
Я спрашиваю людей например с какой с
which animal do you associate yourself with,
каким животным вы себя ассоциируете
for example, a horse or a donkey, that’s
например лошадь да или там ослик вот с
who Which
кем Какой
mouse is not?  a mouse or
нет мышь мышь мышь или
a rat or a rat yes Or a rat I think
крыса или крыса да Или крыса Я думаю
a rat is more suitable And you And I don’t
крыса больше подходит А вы А я не
associate myself with animals I Man
ассоциирую себя с животными я Человек
who is this and that Dear you
кто же это такое-то Милый ты же
actually won’t say anything Well do
вообще-то не буду ничего говорить Ну и
n’t say anything I know that
не говорите я знаю что
yes you  You are very beautiful I know yes I
яный да вы Вы очень красивы Я знаю да Я
will ask you what animal are you
спрошу у вас с каким животным вы себя
sure I don’t associate myself with
уверено не ассоциируюсь я с
animals I am so beautiful that I don’t
животными Я настолько ный что мне не
need to associate myself with animals
нужно ассоциировать себя с животными
think about what you associate yourself with
прикиньте с чем вы себя ассоциируете с
I am so  narcissistic
собой Я настолько самовлюблённый
egocentric narcissist Why do I
эгоцентрической нарцист Да что я себя
associate myself with myself I can’t look I
ассоциирую с собой я не могу смотрите я
tried, I went to a psychologist Yes he
э вот пробовал ходил к психологу Да он
says Andrey about socializing himself with something
говорит Андрей проа соци себя с чем-то
or someone I say I can’t
или с кем-то Я говорю я не могу потому
because how am I going to compare myself  with
что как это я буду сравнивать себя с
something I am This is the ideal of the universe How
чем-то я ж Это идеал мироздания Как я
can I compare myself with something it is not impossible
могу себя сравнить с чем-то не нельзя
therefore I am so ideal that I
поэтому я настолько идеальный что не
cannot compare myself with some third-party
могу себя сравнивать со сторонними
objects or entities name is
какими-то предметами или сущности зовут
Andrey from all this sleep what va  Andrey
Андрей из всего этого спи что ва Андрей
Vasilyevich you can call me Andrey
Васильевич можете звать меня Андрей
Vasilyevich Andrey Vasilyevich Yes, I’m
Васильевич Андрей Васильевич Да я
still so serious in my shirt, I
всё-таки так в рубашечка посерьёзней я
’ll be for you Andrey Vasilyevich
буду для вас Андрей Васильевич
Okay, let’s say Andrey Vasilyevich
Окей давайте скажите Андрей Васильевич
You are very
Вы очень
cool Andrey Vasilyevich
классный Андрей Васильевич
you exceeded my desires Well done There are some
вы вы превысили мои желания Молодец Так
other questions or a couple more
ещё какие-то вопросики есть или ещё пару
compliment me and I'll move
комплименти ков мне и я пойду
on
дальше
Well, I have only one question How is
Ну вопроси ков У меня только один Как у
the weather there?  the weather is not more than
погода погода не ещё чем
me, that’s all that
я это всё что вас
interests you No,
интересует Нет
I ask you a question Andrey Vasilievich
я задать вам вопрос Андрей Васильевич
Vasilyevich Vasilievich
Васильевич Васильевич
Yes, I at least understand
Да я вы хотя бы понимаете
how I apologize now, you do you
как Прошу прощения сейчас на ты ты
understand how you do no no stop stop
понимаешь как ты с не нет стоп стоп
look, let’s still keep
смотри давайте мы всё-таки будем держать
the chain of command Yes  Andrey Vasilyevich you
субординацию Да Андрей Васильевич вы
say Andrey Vasilyevich you are funny
говорите Андрей Васильевич вы смешны
Vasil you understand how funny you are I
Василь вы понимаете как вы смешны Я
understand that you
понимаю что вы
understand Russian
Российска понимаю
and also what else do you understand I don’t know I
а так ещё что вы понимаете Не знаю я
thought that wed It’s not
думал что сре Все не
simple But
просто А
what Who  will pay for this,
что Кто заплатит за это ты
look, you have to be Ilya Kiva to the
посмотри это надо быть Ильёй кивой на
fullest, in short, in order to give your money
всю голову короче чтобы бабки свои
away, you need to pay for it,
отдать за это
I don’t know, I’m saying if
нужно я не знаю говорю если чтобы тебя
someone else pays him moral damage,
кто-то ему ещё моральный ущерб
I agree in general, I totally
платить я согласна вообще я совм
agree to talk to Andrei
согласна чтобы говорить Андрее
Vasilyevich You made me laugh  Senya,
васильевиче Ты меня рассмешила Сеня
just a second. By the way,
просто да секундочку Вот кстати
for not passing the test because we are new, it’s
за не зачёт потому что мы же с вами новы
true. No, we’re not new, you’re
правда так Нет не мы с вами навы вы со
new to me, and I can poke you.
мной навы а я тебе тыкать
No, you  You can’t poke me
могу Нет ты мне тыкать не можешь почему
why Why Because you and I, you and I are
Почему Потому что мы же с тобой мы же с
on you no Look, you’re with me on you And
вами на вы нет Смотри ты со мной на Вы А
I’m with you on
я с тобой на
you no Yes, since a teacher at
ты нет Да так как учитель учитель в
school can say re so Put it down,
школе может сказать ре так Положи а
child,
ребнок
by the way, great I  same teacher You are a
ль кстати отлично я же учитель Ты
teacher as well as a teacher What do you teach at
учительница яже учитель А что ты учишь в
school? I teach mathematics, physics, mathematics,
школе Я учу математику физику математику
physics in high school. Yes, now we will
физику в старших классах Да сейчас мы
integrate you, we will
тебя проинтегрировать
integrate you, no, this is something else, we will
интегрируем вы меня нет это другое
integrate - this is
интегрируем - это
adding K  unfortunately, you don’t know that,
сложить К сожалению вы не знается так не
we don’t tell you about differentiating,
мы вас сначала про дифференцирует
integrating,
проинтегрировать
you won’t be able to because you
вы не сможете потому что у вас
differentiate - What is this? Do you
дифференцировать - Это что такое Вы
know what di is?  we'll
знаете что такое ди вообще не знаю я
do something like this with you, we'll do the second one, we don't need to
сделаем вторую не надо
find the break point for you. Let's
найдём точку разрыва у вас
play with your discriminant. So,
Да поиграемся с вашим дискриминантом Так
yeah, math, damn it, I didn't know that,
Да математички блин не я не знал что
okay, let me do
давай хорошо давайте я сейчас
it now. Let's do it like a teacher.  mathematics, I’m
вас Давайте как учительницу математику я
now exciting you intellectually,
сейчас вас интеллектуально
what will be equal to what will be
возбуждаю чему будет равно чему будет
equal to 3 by
равно 3 по
0 Oh, you can’t divide one by zero for a second
0 Ой секундочку одну на ноль делить
You’re definitely a
нельзя Вы точно учительница
math teacher, son here I have a
математики сын вот тут у меня вообще
wonderful person in general How much will 3
замечательный человек Сколько будет 3
by 3 be
по 3 по
nuni Oh hello again What’s on
нуни Ой здравствуйте ещ раз А что по на
But  and what Where do such smart questions
Но а что Откуда такие умные вопросы на
come from when dividing by zero doesn’t say that there’s something like that
ноль делить не говорит что что-то такое
there? Well, little one Give me Oksana
там вот не Ну малой Дай мне Оксану
back here, my son sm lay down In short, you and I
назад здесь сын мой см легла Короче мы с
Shura  t sym gla bearded koro
тобой Шуры а т сым гла бородатым коро
he lies in the crib with his
он лежит в кроватке с
mother I
мамой мне
Diy for many years How old are you
Дий много лет Сколько тебе
Oksanochka doesn’t want to talk
лет не хочет разговаривать Оксаночка
How old is this tenchi of yours who is lying with his
Сколько лет этому твоему тенчи который с
mother like
мамочкой типа
how old is he
лежит сколько ему
28 28 he
лет 28 28 он мамой
lives with his mother Yes everything is correct
живёт Да всё правильно
Adele Well, this is usually not surprising  I
адел Ну бы это обычно не удивительно
usually know men at 28 years old with their mother and they
обычно зна мужики в 28 лет с мамо и
live, you know,
живут знаеш
look, if we take for example that for
бы смотри если условно взять то что
example you have a one-room apartment,
например у тебя однокомнатная квартира
of course you can’t live with your mother  cool, but a
конечно с мамой жить не прикольно но
huge house,
огромный дом
such an approach to family life, we kind of live in a
такай подход к семеной жиз мы типа живём
big clan, what’s the problem and who
большим кланом в чём проблема кла а кто
else is in your
ещё в вашем
clan Well,
клане Ну те
everyone Yes, I want how big your
все Да я хочу насколько У вас большой
clan is, can you
клан можешь
explain in this house? In principle, everyone is
объяснить в этом доме В принципе все
close Well, who is who?
близкие Ну кто кто да
List more  since mom dad
Перечисли ещё раз мама папа
grandma I mean, you
бабушка Я то есть жены у тебя
don’t have a wife, you don’t have a girlfriend, she lives with you
нет жены нет есть девушка она с тобой
Yes, with mom and
живёт Да с мамой и
grandma mom and grandma
бабушкой мамой и бабушкой
Yes, he doesn’t understand Don’t wait, no question I’m
Да он не понимает Не подожди не вопрос Я
not really me at all  I don’t understand Look,
вообще не я реально не понимаю Смотри у
I just didn’t have such a
меня просто не было такого
traumatic experience to live with my mother
травматического опыта чтобы жить с мамой
and grandmother Yes, when an adult is like, well,
и бабушкой Да когда взрослый как бы ну
like You’re probably unlucky with your
типа Тебе наверное не повезло с
relatives, you don’t have
родственниками у тебя нет с ними
normal relations with them Well, yes, there are no
нормальных отношений Ну да ской нет
relatives in such a hut that
родственников тако хатой чтобы там жило
less than 20 people would live there  like yes No, it’s
короче 20 человек типа да Нету
really not about the house. The point is that
реально дело не в хате Дело в том что у
your relationship with
тебя просто не выстроенные отношения с
yours is simply not built, yes yes it’s not built,
твоими не выстроены да да не выстроены у
we somehow don’t build it. Here I am and with my
нас как-то не выстраивают Вот я и У моих
friends  for some reason, everyone is not lined up
знакомых почему-то не выстроены все
somehow, they don’t line up that in short they are
как-то так не выстраивают что короче им
getting a few years old and they somehow don’t
встаёт немножко лет и они как-то не
live with their
живут с
parents. Well, that means it’s like that with us, so
родителями Ну значит у вас так у нас так
he doesn’t understand one thing, I don’t understand. Well, I
он не понима одного я не понимаю Вот я я
don’t understand. Look, here’s mine  Mom, for
не понимаю Смотри вот моей маме да
example, she’s been there for a lot of years, right now she would be
например там кучу лет она вот сейчас бы
with someone with some guy in the bazaars,
с кем-то с каким-то мужиком базари
in short, on the phone, then she came to the
короче по телефону потом пришла на
bed in the room and lay down in a pose with my man,
кроватку комне легла поза с моим мужиком
well, this is In short, some kind of simple
ну это Короче какая-то просто
Dude, this is just damn  really, damn
Чувак это просто блин реально разнос
where did they switch, subscribe to my
куда переключились блин подпишись на мий
Telegram right now, the axis of wine and
Telegram прям зараз ось вин а
pok tse even more and more respectfully YouTube banning
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube ганя
us through skarg or in your ban and even
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people at the moment I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams For this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose, we need Mali operational sound  'language to
того щоб ми Мали оперативний зв'язок
be written directly at once while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okrim video more  tezh tsikava and korisna
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we will
информация и мы повинни з вами трима
show you about it YouTube
в того чи покаже вам про це YouTube
Glory to Ukraine subscribe
Слава Украине подпишись